<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prakash Paudel</title>
    <link>https://prakashpaudel.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Prakash Paudel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 06:42:21 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://prakashpaudel.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bookshelf</title>
      <link>https://prakashpaudel.com/bookshelf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 11:22:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prakashpaudel.com/bookshelf/</guid>
      <description>I was inspired by patrick collison who shared a virtual bookshelf reflecting his real bookshelf.
I don&amp;rsquo;t maintain a real life bookshelf since I move around often. But, here&amp;rsquo;s some books that I&amp;rsquo;ve read recently. I&amp;rsquo;ve bolded the ones I find especially great. These are in no specific order.
 1984, George Orwell Sapiens, Yuval Harari Kafka By the Sea, Haruki Murakami Norwegian Wood, Haruki Murakami Vagabonding, Rolf Potts Steppenwolf, Hermann Hesse Siddhartha, Hermann Hesse The Autobiography of Gucci Mane Brave New World, Aldous Huxley Selfish Gene, Richard Dawkins The Travelers, Chris Pavone Asimov Short stories, Isaac Asimov Anti-fragile, Nassim Taleb Demian, Hermann Hesse Heart of Darkness, Joseph Conrad The Communist Manifesto, Karl Marx The Wind-Up Bird Chronicle, Haruki Murakami Bullshit Jobs, David Graeber A Brief History Of Time, Stephen Hawking The Count of Monte Cristo, Alexandre Dumas Guns, Sails and Empires, Carlo Cipolla Debt: The first 5,000 years, David Graeber Skin in the Game, Nassim Taleb The French Revolution and What Went Wrong, Stephen Clarke My Life in Red and White, Arsène Wenger  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A World Cup To Remember: 2002</title>
      <link>https://prakashpaudel.com/blog/a-world-cup-to-remember-2002/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 17:09:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prakashpaudel.com/blog/a-world-cup-to-remember-2002/</guid>
      <description>After 4 weeks and over 100 hours of football, the World Cup is coming to an end. One of France, Belgium, Croatia or England will be crowned World Champions this Sunday.
It&amp;rsquo;s been a tournament to remember. There are goals, moments and games I will never forget. I wanted to share some memories from my very first World Cup, the first one of the new millennium. World Cup 2002.
I was 8 years old in 2002.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arsène Wenger</title>
      <link>https://prakashpaudel.com/blog/arsene-wenger/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 06:51:33 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prakashpaudel.com/blog/arsene-wenger/</guid>
      <description>Last week, Arsène Wenger managed his last game for Arsenal Football Club. He&amp;rsquo;s been manager of the team for 22 years. I want to write a bit about what it&amp;rsquo;s been like to follow Arsenal and Monsieur Wenger all these years.
As a young kid growing up in Asia, becoming an Arsenal fan was by chance. I didn&amp;rsquo;t have any connection to the club. I just watched whatever match was on TV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google&#39;s Phone AI</title>
      <link>https://prakashpaudel.com/blog/googles-phone-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 12:12:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prakashpaudel.com/blog/googles-phone-ai/</guid>
      <description>Last week, google showed off a really cool demo phone call. Google&amp;rsquo;s AI called a hair salon to setup an appointment. It went something like this:
AI: Hello, I&amp;#39;d like to make a hair appointment for my client for, umm, the Wednesday the 7th for 12pm. Salon (Actual person): Ok. Give me oneee second. AI: mmhhmm Salon: We don&amp;#39;t have anything for 12, we do have a 1:15. AI: Umm, I&amp;#39;m looking for something between 10-12 actually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://prakashpaudel.com/blog/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 17:09:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prakashpaudel.com/blog/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my personal site. It&amp;rsquo;s built with hugo, a nifty framework for generating static sites.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
